isisi Lombard a leading private General
insurer in India proudly announces the
launch of its revolutionary health
insurance product Elevate powered with
AI this first of its kind Health product
is loaded with Cutting Edge features and
add-ons offering personalized solutions
to meet the needs of a dynamic lifestyle
unforeseen medical emergencies and
medical inflation this significant
launch underscores isisi Lombard's
commitment to pioneering advancements in
the insurance industry and delivering
exceptional value to its customers
designed to cater to the rapidly
evolving ecosystem Elevate offers a
suite of personalized customer Centric
plans that prioritize comprehensive
coverage and
flexibility the key features of elevate
include AI powered personalization
utilizes Advanced AI algorithms to
analyze individual health data and
lifestyle patterns creating tailored
plans that best meet the unique needs of
each customer comprehensive coverage
offers extensive coverage options that
address a wide range of medical
conditions and emergencies ensuring that
customers are well protected in any
situation flexibility and customization
provides flexible policy terms and
customizable add-ons allowing customers
to adapt their insurance plans as their
needs change over time preventive health
benefits includes features that promote
preventive Health Care encouraging
regular checkups and wellness activities
to maintain Optimal Health seamless
digital experience ensures a
userfriendly and efficient digital
platform for policy purchase management
and claims processing enhancing overall
customer convenience the Vex rasav head
health agency isisi Lombard stated
Elevate is a testament to our dedication
to Innovation and customer
centricity by leveraging AI we are able
to offer highly personalized Insurance
Solutions that adapt to the changing
needs of our customers the no Mahajan
Chief investment officer isisi Lombard
added with the no Mahajan Chief
investment officer isisi Lombard added
with Elevate we are setting a new
Benchmark in the health insurance sector
this product not only provides robust
Financial Protection but also empowers
customers to take charge of their health
proactively the introduction of elevate
marks a significant milestone in issi
Lombard's Journey reinforcing its
position as a forward-thinking leader in
the insurance industry the company
remains committed to continuously
evolving and enhancing its offerings to
meet the diverse needs of its customers
health insurance product uh thank you
first of all and I think uh there are
many unique features in this product uh
uh first of all the this is a completely
modular in nature the product which we
have designed the name of the product is
Elevate uh the key add-ons the features
which we have introduced in this product
one is a infinite care cover which is
given to the customers in this cover we
are introducing industry first feature
which is in the lifetime of the policy
customer can request and Avail claim of
any unlimited amount but but it can be
claimed only once throughout the
lifetime of the policy this cover today
is not available in the industry itself
so this is a very unique cover which is
there and for the very first time IC mod
is really proud to have introduced for
the larger audience of the market so how
does the infinite some Ure future
benefit policy holders uh see today
largely whatever products are available
in the market uh maximum uh have a
capping that tell you that today the
some insured can be 5 lakh or 10 LH or
20 lakh or 30 lakh or 50 lakh something
of that sort uh typically any any good
customer would always want to have a
security a peace of mind that what if my
claim amount or if I want to uh get a
higher some insured to to to solve that
Pro problem what we have done is we have
introduced unlimited some insured option
in our new product elevate here customer
can has a option to choose from 5 lakhs
some insurance to up till unlimited
times cust some insurance whatever he
wants to choose from so this is for the
very first time uh and it's a industry
leading uh feature which we have
introduced in our product so what makes
the power booster add on significant
addition to the Elevate plan uh again uh
as you know we are a we are we are a big
population in our country uh we are
number one population wise our country
right now has one out of three people
are suffering from diabetes and it is
growing day by day uh as that population
is growing and then there are so many uh
ailments which are coming there are so
many uh things which are people are
suffering from all those customers today
typically in any health insurance plans
has to wait for a certain time to get
those ailments covered in their normal
policy by virtue of elevate by virtue of
jump start add-on which we have given in
our product this waiting period is now
getting reduced to 31 days so that is
the unique feature which is again there
in our product
Elevate so what type of coverage does
elevate provide so it provide a very
comprehensive coverage it is completely
modular it is very much
personalized uh it has so many options
for any customer to optain he can select
whatever he wants uh from a variety of
add-on functions which are most most of
them are best in class uh new to the
industry or or best in the industry so
it is given a complete a complete peace
of mind and more importantly a wide
range of options to choose
from uh sir what is the advantage of
infinite Assurance add on for
individuals with pre-existing conditions
so as I said this is this is one uh jump
start feature which is there which we
call jump start it gives the flexibility
of to customer to start to get their PDS
covered from very 31st day so that is
the feature there is a thing which which
is getting covered from 31st day all PDS
will get covered in this plan the launch
of elevate considered aing step in the
health insurance industry according to
ICI number so the Elevate product is an
industry first as VI also mentioned none
of the companies have been offering such
an unlimited cover to any uh you know
policy holder so that is why I Lombard
feels that uh it is a very unique
positioning of the you know in the
health insurance industry it's a
revolutionary product for the health
insurance industry and it will benefit
the
customer so how does elate c to need for
personalized Health Insurance Solutions
so the base plan which is there a
customer can choose a base plan and on
top of that he can add any options which
he wants rather than taking a customized
uh rather than taking a standard on
product which is available in the market
year he can customize according to his
needs or his future requirements that is
why it's a different product completely
how does the integration in El enhance
the health insurance experience of for
customers yes I think we are really very
excited because this is the first
product in the market which is bagged or
enabled by AI what we have done since
this product gives power to to customer
to choose from variety of options which
are available uh at times we think that
mean there has to be some recommendation
which should go from our side to the
customer what he should
buy so what we have done is we have
basis the personas of customer we have
we have uh integrated our systems their
algorithms which are made and hence in
our systems for any customer we are
recommending a plan with some add-ons
which he should be buying basis our
recommendation tool basis his demography
this is his uh other personas which are
we are capturing at the time of sale so
in a way we are trying to help customer
out to tell him that hey look these are
the add-ons you should buy but this is
just a recommendation still customer has
full choice to add or delete whatever he
wants so my last question is like what
makes the power booster add on a
significant addition to the elate plan
it is very unique feature in the market
because power booster is one feature
which gives
a bonus of 100% year on year typically
in our Market uh the bonus which is
given is to the tune of 2x 4X 5x or at
in sometimes up till 10x there's a
limitation to that in our product we
have said irrespective of claim your
bonus will keep on increasing year on
year up to unlimited time so it will
keep on growing until you keep on
renewing the policy so as simple as that
and again this is industry first feature
which we have launched in our product
[Music]